

Yuri Pereira



My Objective

I'm a person that are always looking forward of something innovative. I've founded my consulting online business in september of 2014, aimed in change the practices among health & Fitness in a digital way and live new challenging experiences. Focused now on my improvements in server-side skills using Node, is and Angular, is besides working with Front-end development for more than 4 years.



Educational Qualification

Computer Systems [August 2015 - Currently]

B.sc Computer Science [August 2010 - January 2015]

Universidade Federal Fluminense - UFF Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro - UERI

High School Computer Technician [January 2006- December 2008] Colégio Senhora da Pena



Professional Experience

Trainee Full-Stack Web Developer [January 2015 - Currently]

Work on maintance project of channels of TV group GLOBOSAT. My function range to create new features and hotfixes for all of the current projects of TV group GLOBOSAT, e.g.; Sexy hot channel, Telecine channel, GNT, Multishow and others

Project Leader CAPGOV [June 2014 - August 2015]

I Worked as a leader of new project of CAPGOV, collaborating for the creation of a new page and system inserted on the context of new technologies and raised their rank using SEO techniques, Managing a small team,

Intern of web development [February 2011 - June 2014] CAPGOV - COPPE - LIER I



Skills

Gulp/Tasks

Proficiency Photoshop HTML5 PHP/SOL Js/Jauery





Brazilian

English(fluent), Spanish



Naturality

- Lecture Digital Design
- Tecnology Travel
- Fitness



- Autodidact
- Sociability
- Ágile Development



Telefone

Email

Weh www.yuriramos.com